Suppose that Audacity sometimes includes promotions for
假设优达学城有时候会在免费课程的视频旁边
their coaching next to the videos in their free courses.
为其辅导课程做推广
The promotion might say something like,
推广文案可能是
do you need some help with this material?
需要有人指导你学习此课程吗？
Contact one of our coaches.
请联系我们的辅导员
They run an experiment changing the wording of this message and
他们就更改推广文案开展了一个实验
they use click-through-rate as their metric.
并使用点击率作为指标
Now since the unit of analysis is a pageview
由于分析单元是页面查看
Audacity also might want to make the unit of diversion a pageview.
所以优达学城可能将分组单元设置为页面查看
However, they might also want to consider using a cookie to get a more
然而 他们可能还考虑使用 cookie
consistent experience.
为用户提供更一致的体验
Let's see how that would affect the size of the experiment.
我们来看看这对实验规模有何影响
If you calculate the variability analytically, it won't change between
如果计算分析差异性
the two units of diversion but for the cookie-based diversion,
这两种分组单元之间并无变化 但对于基于 cookie 的分组方式
the analytic estimate is likely to be an under-estimate.
分析估计的结果可能是估计不足
So Audacity does an empirical estimate of the variability with 5,000 page
所以优达学城对每组 5,000 次页面查看的差异性
views in each group.
做了一个经验估计
First they randomly sample by page view to simulate the unit of diversion being
首先 他们按页面查看进行随机取样 模拟基于页面查看的分组单元
a pageview and they get a standard deviation of 0.00515.
获得的标准偏差为 0.00515
Then they randomly sample by cookie to get a different set of pageviews and
然后 他们按 cookie 进行随机取样 获得另一组页面查看数据
the standard deviation is 0.0119.
获得的标准偏差为 0.0119
Now that's quite a difference but
这两个数据的差异很显著
how will it actually affect the size of the experiment?
这将如何对实验规模产生实际影响？
In order to calculate the size, we can assume that the standard error for
为了计算规模 我们可以假设实验的标准误差
the experiment is proportional to one over the square root of the sample size.
与样本量的平方根成比例
That means that as you vary the sample size the standard error would look like
就是说 改变样本量时 基于 cookie 的分组单元的标准误差将是这样
this for the cookie and the pageview units of diversion.
而基于页面查看的分组单元的标准误差将是这样
As in the graph before, the x axis is 1 over the square route of N so
和之前的图表一样 X 轴等于样本量 N 的平方根分之一
the standard error follows a straight line.
所以标准误差会是一条直线
Using this information about how the standard error varies with
根据标准误差与样本量的关系
the sample size, you can calculate the size that would be needed.
我们可以计算出所需的实验规模
If you want to see how to do this, you can look at the r code linked in
如果想要了解如何计算
the instructor's notes which will do the calculation.
请参阅讲师备注中链接的 r 代码
In this case, lets say that the practical significance boundary, or
在这个例子中 我们假设实际显著性界线
d min is 0.02.
也就是 dmin 等于 0.02
Then if Audacity used pageview as the unit of diversion,
如果优达学城使用页面查看作为分组单元
they would need about 2,600 page views to get enough power.
他们需要拥有大约 2,600 个页面查看才能获得见解
But if they diverted by cookie, they would need about 13,900 pageviews,
如果使用 cookie 作为分组单元 他们就需要大约 13,900 个页面查看
which is a huge difference.
这之间的差异很大
In cases like these, you probably need to actually plug the numbers
在这种情况下 你可能需要计算出这些数字才能了解准确的实验规模
in to get the exact size, but it's also important to have an intuition for
但根据直觉来判断变更将如何影响规模
how this type of change will affect sizing.
也很重要
That way you can quickly decide which changes are worth considering and
从而你可以快速确定哪种变更才是值得考虑的
when you look at your data you know whether its plausible or not, and
查看数据时 你就能知道它是否可行
the way to build intuition is by getting lots of practice.
培养直觉的方法就是多加练习